We have lost the slop wars.
Most people are no longer able to tell what is AI generated and what is not.
I can confirm that this is 100% true, let me prove it right now.
So this character is blowing up on the internet right now.
He's amassed 240,000 followers in the last like seven days and so what I did was I came
and I clicked.
I copy and pasted the link to this video and I put it into my codex and I said, um, what
did I say?
Hey, can you make a photorealistic character sheet of this man and that's what it did.
Look at this.
Okay.
I brought that into Higgsfield.
So now it's into Higgsfield.
This is where all the magic happens.
Higgsfield just released their newest model called like Genjutsu.
It's insane.
I mean, there's no other way to describe it.
So I inputted the character sheet.
I wanted to like create a viral video just to see like how potent this can be.
And so I took like two viral elements, right?
I took this guy who's super trending right now.
I was originally going to do a cyber taxi because like that's kind of pop in these days,
but I figured cyber truck is more recognizable as it stands.
So I went and created a cyber truck character sheet.
I brought that into my video generation.
Basically I just put it into here.
I came and I found this viral video, which you may or may not know of.
This old grandpa telling somebody to stop fishing while he's being fishing.
This is going micro viral right now.
So what I did was I basically prompted Higgsfield to remove the white pickup truck and
replace it with a cyber truck and remove the old man with this character that is going
viral.
And look at this product.
The product is insane.
And listen, I'm going to let you watch the full video because I posted it on my Instagram
and it's blowing up right now.
But it also, I posted it on my TikTok and it is going mega viral right now.
And so this is confirmed.
Thank you.
And a lot of the comments in my TikTok are like, yo, this is the most real AI I've ever
seen or they don't even understand that it's AI to begin with.
So we're moving into interesting times here.
Yeah, but I mean, I tested this theory last night.
When I had the video saved in my photos app,
I knew that this would go viral.
Because it can't not.
I'm combining multiple viral elements.
And it did.
It's doing half a million on TikTok right now.
I think we're at 40,000 on Instagram and trending upwards.
So crazy.
I want to end this on a high note here.
And so the through line is we want to elevate ourselves from mindless consumers to leverages
of these really advanced AI technologies.
How do we do that?
You gotta get involved.
You gotta get privy to this.
You gotta learn.
You gotta build.
You gotta have fun.
You gotta experiment.
You gotta reach out.
You gotta learn.
You gotta educate yourself.
It's happening right now.
And if you don't, you're going to be stuck at the bottom like things are going to be
happening above you and then they're going to kind of come down and be injected into
your brain because you're not going to have a capacity to think beyond what you're being
fed.
Learn.
Play.
Grow.